well I'm gonna run the base...
or... next to the green run button
from the arrow pointing down we choose the TaskA configuration from the dropdown menu
[sighs]
from the dropdown menu choose
okay
[Clicks on the TaskA test] [runs the test]
now I'm waiting for it to finish running
I can see this is a maven project
though I could guess that from the
src/main/java structure and
from POM
It's interesting though, because the JRE system library says Java 1.6
but here it was run with 1.7
[clears his throat]
well anyway
I'll look into this
okay here I can see
it deleted them
[adjusts glasses]
I'll search for
in math
the... erm
NumberUtils.java
but otherwise you should search for it in the test
but for this
Java class (unintelligible)... you can make sense of the test
I will open these
and I'll search for the testCreatNumber test
this is a constructor
testToInt
string
this is a relatively long file so I will
search with ctrl+f
umm... I hope this will work
I'm looking for the test [types]
Creat, but anyway in eclipse there should be an option to see
the functions
in Window maybe editor
show view and here is one called
not project
buut
expressions maybe
nope nope nope nope
I want to see somewhere the...
what this contains
never mind, I'll just search for it instead of wasting more time on it, because I don't know how they
planned this one and a half hour