Okay, then let's see the next such (instructor)
case, let's say that during the task you solved (instructor)
last time, when you wanted to examine the errors (instructor)
within the project (instructor)
loading the list would have taken 5 minutes (instructor)
meanwhile the Eclipse development environment wouldn't respond to commands (instructor)
how would this have affected you? (instructor)
Well, uuuh,
I had such a, well not exactly this issue
but... I had library problems, for me
it explicitly underlined the
I think the stringUtilst
and uuuh, when you have a specific task, then those
errors that do not belong there can be really annoying [laughs]
and then others also come out, obviously a project clean and
etc. can solve this, usually, in Eclipse
But otherwise, yeah, it annoys me a little
or if there are those that,
well, that are quite unexpected, that for
completely separate reasons
just a kind of fiddling around, like let's say
the development environment is how it is, or the
the development tool, or the computer, or the
whatever else, then that can annoy me
quite a lot
I’m not saying it would specifically negatively affect it,
because this usually
does occur, so it is a typical developer error
So it's not that negative, rather it just causes
stressful situations, especially if you have a deadline
and here I imagine this as
a deadline, because time
there is a time limit
during which you should be finished, and my expectation is that I want to be able to finish
it might just be because of this, or if somebody
I'm sure there are people to whom
to whom it doesn't matter, because they don't care
about it, to me this is more like a competition
this situation [laughs] and so
I want to do it well, and then
every other such thing bothers me.
so this is how it affects me, it's like
it like creates a stressful situation, yeah.