Okay, well erm, now we'll try to use this iFL - oh I still haven't selected the project
Okay, here are the failed tests
iFL [clicks]
Erm, yes, so now I selected the project in iFL, erm, okay
[waits]
We're gonna test what this tool is good for, now that I know how
how it works.
Well this puts it in a different context now that I know how it works
[makes faces while waiting]
But sadly the...
... the tool is not too, tool fast [laughs at pun]
Whoops [looks at the results]
[looks at the results] Now it's showing us something
[looks at the results]
Maybe if it's in the project root it will load automatically?
Because, erm... [clicks]
[clicks] Because yesterday, well never mind, I'll click on Load scores again
Uuuuuh, [clicks]
[clicks]
Okay, well it says that [clicks] based on the score
I'll put it in order
from top to bottom
there's only one problem with this, which is that the signature is ... mhm
Well it's... scrollable
The error will be at Fraction
the Fraction's test ... yeah
let's look at this... erm
I double click it, right? Then it will jump to it?
Does it also open it? Or just...if it's open will it jump to it? No, it also opens it, awesome
Uuuh, okay, so theoretically this
[looks at the plugin] in this test there are errors
[looks at the plugin]
[mumbles] fraction, fraction, fraction....
let's see
Name: reduce
It's a bit lower, okay, it's quite big
[clicks] Well...
[clicks]
Well this is... [mumbles] maybe there won't be errors in (unintelligible)
But these are, pretty big [keeps clicking]
...pretty big methods
getNumerator, there won't be errors in this one
I will go on and lower its score
How did it go? Maybe you just need to... [clicks]
[clicks]
[clicks, looks at the plugin]
[looks at the method, clicks] that's it
Erm [reads the function]
Context feedback... good
So I will lower this, I won't modify the others yet, but I'll lower this, 'cause
this definitely won't have errors.
getter
[keeps clicking]
[mumbles] Mutable ... oh yes, here with
the ordering - I would report a bug with iFL that if you modify the context, then the
ordering will disappear, Denominator
[clicks] erm
I could do multimple ones at the same time
erm Fraction, here well, I suppose there won't be any errors here either
erm... getReduceFraction
... here the rows are a little skewed, Position, but whatever, I found these, this is fine