So, our first case is (instructor)
no. 17075, and it goes like (instructor) [ambulance sirens outside]
like 'WEE-oww', let's wait this out (instructor)
Alright, so 17075, the methods are (instructor)
in a descending order based on score (instructor)
in the iFL tool (instructor)
and you can find the createNumber method in 7th place in this (instructor)
list that is in a des... descending order based on score. (instructor)
So it's on the first page (instructor)
- it's the penultimate out of the 8 cards (instructor)
- The last one, yeah
Uuuuh, let's say that this is the method with the error (instructor)
so before this one you already had to examine 6 other methods (instructor)
erm, there were some here like
it's one of the bugs from Monday, I don't know how well you remember it (instructor)
it was full of these create...
- methods, createFloat, createBiginteger, and ... (instructor)
- Yes-yes
nonessestial stuff like that (instructor)
- bigDecimal and whatnot (instructor)
- Yes-yes
so this is the situation that there is (instructor)
this page full of methods in iFL, the 7th is the (instructor)
the penultimate is the (instructor)
the createNumber, of which we later (instructor)
learn that it is the one with the error, but you don't know that yet (instructor)
uuh, and by the time you get there (instructor)
now let's assume that you insist (instructor)
well maybe not insist, but you use iFL's list  (instructor)
to help you, and you already had to examine (instructor)
six methods, by the time you finally end up with (instructor)
the one that has the errors. (instructor)
[he thinks]
Erm, and so...
What is the question? [laughs]
Yeah, I know, there is no question... well erm
- Well basically... what is your opinion about the situation, does it affect you (instructor)
- I see
- in any way...? (instructor)
- Well the problem is that...
I didn't exactly understand, or like... I don't know
if I should have understood, what, what this tool
erm, what it does, or rather how does it do...
well how much, uuh
can you, uuh
rely on it, so
If it's important to you, then I can tell you how (instructor)
those lists come to be (instructor)
Well, uuuuuh... yeah.
So this is a ... this technique is called (instructor)
spectrum-based fault localization (instructor)
where the spectrum and the coverage
- Mhm
- well technically the spectrum is the coverage, there's only (instructor)
one twist in the whole thing, (instructor)
namely that we are not looking at how you run the test suite and so what that covers (instructor)
but instead for each test you determine the (instructor)
what they cover, so what methods (instructor)
and from this you'll have a freaking huge matrix (instructor)
and we also have which methods, or I mean which tests (instructor)
ran with what results, whether they passed or failed (instructor)
Erm, and then you can get all sorts of interesting statistics from this (instructor)
there are thousands of millions of formulas for how you (instructor)
eventually calculate the score from this amount of data, but the (instructor)
basic assumption is that (instructor)
the most suspicious, so the method with the highest score (instructor)
erm, is the one on which only failing tests pass (instructor)
so you run the failing test and what (instructor)
- that touches on is suspicious. (instructor)
- Yes.
you can add nuance to this by (instructor)
also running passed tests (instructor)
and they also touch on the ones that (instructor)
the failing ones did too, then there it drops a bit, so it's different... (instructor)
Mhm, so there are tests that
pass and
- is included in them, mhm.
- And it includes what the failing did as well (instructor)
...soo let's say you have three methods, A, B, and C (instructor)
these are covered by the failing one (instructor)
and you have two other tests that also touch on B and C (instructor)
and they passed. (instructor)
Then the assumption is (instructor)
that A is more suspicious than B or C because that one (instructor)
was only included in the failing test (instructor)
then there really are thousands of millions of formulas (instructor)
to precisely take advantage or to calculate this (instructor)
Uuuuh, and then these (instructor)
result in a score, usually between 0-1 (instructor)
uh, and then that makes the list (instructor)
Mhm, and that csv, that scores
is that... that, how does that connect
- to this, is that the output of some...
- Yes it connects to this by... (instructor)
Yes, so this is a pretty slow and lengthy measurement process (instructor)
by the time these scores are produced, because it's freaking huge (instructor)
Ah, so it's calculated beforehand
- and then this is the result.
- And then (instructor)
- this is the result. (instructor)
- Ah, I see.
Mhm.
Do you want me to read the situation again? (instructor)
Uuuuh, no you don't have to, so
the point is that... that our affected
method is relatively
it's in the penultimate position in the top...
- 8, yeah (instructor)
- top 8, mhm. [thinks]
- Well whether it's the penultimate or not... (instructor)
- Yeah yeah, it's at the end, yeah
[thinks]
So for this, in this case you can
well obviously, if I know that
that that is the method that interests me,
but then I clearly already got there, like let's say I looked at the first one
or the ones before it
and then I could use that tool
to set the score, uuuuh
- ratios? or
- With percentages, you can decrease or increase... (instructor)
Okay, then I could pretty much do that
I would either increase its score,
compared to the others', compared to the ones before or
- or I could lower the score of the previous ones'?
- Exactly (instructor)
And by the way is that only for
only good for
let's say pulling my
or the affected method forward?
Yyyyyes, yeah-yeahs. (instructor)
but so this is not for some kind of training
- this is just for the given display....
- This is just static, yeah-yeah (instructor)
It's an interesting aspect, (instructor)
I'm gonna jot that down (instructor) [they laugh]
- that uuuuh (instructor)
- So this is just about like, like
get these out of here, I don't care about them, but let's say, bring
- those forward that are more interesting to me.
- Obviously you don't know from the get go what (instructor)
- you'll find (instructor)
- Yeah, you just make those disappear that
Mhm, that are no longer... mhm
... you can weigh them, or even completely rule them out (instructor)
and then the others come forward. (instructor)
[thinks]